=Love For Two Lives=
= الحب لعمرين =
=Episode 17=
= الحلقة 17 =
I heard
سمعت
that those bandits are brutal.
أن هؤلاء اللصوص هم وحشيون.
Bandits?
قطاع الطرق؟
Does Your Highness know their whereabouts?
هل تعرف سموك مكان وجودهم؟
How would I know?
كيف لي ان اعرف؟
You really don't know, Your Highness?
أنت حقا لا تعرف ، صاحب السمو؟
Is it that you don't know
هل أنت لا تعرف
or you just don't want to tell me?
أو فقط لا تريد أن تخبرني؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
Fine.
بخير.
Since Your Highness refused to tell,
منذ أن رفض صاحب السمو أن يقول ،
let it be, then.
فليكن ، إذن.
It's late.
الوقت متاخر.
I won't bother you anymore.
لن أزعجك بعد الآن.
General.
عام.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Farewell.
وداع.
Young Mistress.
عشيقة شابة.
Young Master is ill.
السيد الشاب مريض.
I feel sorry for you.
أشعر بالأسف من أجلك.
The night of pleasure is always too short.
دائمًا ما تكون ليلة المتعة قصيرة جدًا.
I'll leave you alone now.
سأتركك وحدك الآن.
I'm sorry about this.
انني اسف لذلك.
This is what they do in all the shows.
هذا ما يفعلونه في كل العروض.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
This room is not windproof at all.
هذه الغرفة ليست مقاومة للرياح على الإطلاق.
No wonder you're having a fever.
لا عجب أنك تعاني من الحمى.
Thankfully, I always bring medicine with me.
لحسن الحظ ، أنا دائمًا أحمل معي الدواء.
Here.
هنا.
That's it.
هذا هو.
You've taken the medicine.
لقد تناولت الدواء.
You'll recover in no time.
سوف تتعافى في أي وقت من الأوقات.
I'm off now.
لقد انتهيت الأن.
Take care.
يعتني.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
It's you.
انه انت.
Are you really going to let me serve you?
هل حقا ستدعني أخدمك؟
Shut up now.
اصمت الآن.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Didn't you say
لم تقل
you are going to be the future queen.
ستصبحين ملكة المستقبل.
You shouldn't take anything from other men.
لا يجب أن تأخذ أي شيء من الرجال الآخرين.
He's not just some other man.
إنه ليس مجرد رجل آخر.
(Princess Fei'er is the kindest lady I've ever met.)
(الأميرة فايير هي ألطف سيدة قابلتها في حياتي).
(She's as pure as the moon in the sky.)
(إنها نقية مثل القمر في السماء.)
I'm going to General Sa.
أنا ذاهب إلى الجنرال سا.
General Sa.
العامة سا.
I have something to tell you.
لدي شيء لأخبرك به.
What is it, Your Highness?
ما الأمر يا صاحب السمو؟
General Sa.
العامة سا.
I know I'm wrong.
أعلم أنني مخطئ.
But I don't have other choices.
لكن ليس لدي خيارات أخرى.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
I don't think
لا اعتقد
we have anything to say to each other anymore.
لدينا ما نقوله لبعضنا البعض بعد الآن.
General Sa.
العامة سا.
I'll tell you where the Queen is.
سأخبرك أين الملكة.
Good dog.
كلب جيد.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Don't bark.
لا تنبح.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
Good dog.
كلب جيد.
Please stop.
توقف أرجوك.
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
We will get caught because of a dog.
سوف يُقبض علينا بسبب كلب.
You two!
أنت أيضا!
Where do you think you're going?
أين تعتقد أنك ذاهب؟
No, no.
مهووس.
Calm down.
هدء من روعك.
You want to run away?
تريد أن تهرب؟
Kill them.
اقتلهم.
Please don't.
من فضلك لا.
Who dares to touch my Queen!
من يجرؤ على لمس ملكتي!
♪Traces of time and space, and forgotten galaxies♪
آثار الزمان والمكان ، والمجرات المنسية
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
الوقت يتناوب علاقتنا ♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪ بحر النجوم جميل وهادئ
♪The rain touches the breath♪
المطر يمس النفس ♪
Liangliang.
ليانجليانج.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
Are you hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
You're finally here, Your Majesty.
أنت هنا أخيرًا يا صاحب الجلالة.
It's okay.
حسنا.
Wait.
انتظر.
You are the King?
أنت الملك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
- You are the Queen? - Yeah.
- انت الملكة؟  - نعم.
Rebellious rascals!
الأوغاد المتمردين!
How dare you still be standing?
كيف تجرؤ على البقاء واقفا؟
How dare you bring a few minions
كيف تجرؤ على إحضار بعض التوابع
and pretend to be the King?
ويتظاهر بأنه الملك؟
I'm the boss here.
أنا الرئيس هنا.
The Young Master is awake!
السيد الشاب مستيقظ!
The Young Master is awake?
السيد الشاب مستيقظ؟